{ lively chatter )
{ chatter continues )
{ echoing laughter )
- ( chime ) - ( automated voice ) Till number one .
{ machine whirs )
Good morning , sir , welcome to Waingel 's Bank .
My name is Sheila . How can I help you ?
{ choral music plays )
{ phone rings )
01632 960786 ?
- ( man ) You all righl ? - Yeah , all right . You ?
- ( man ) Yeah , yeah . - Do you want me to get him ?
- ( man ) Uh , yeah . - Vince ! Vince ! Telephone !
- ( Vince ) Is that Gwen ? - No , your dad .
- All right ? - ( man ) Don 'task . You ?
( laughs ) Yeah , you ?
( choral music continues )
( Vince laughs in distance )
( synth music )
( footsteps )
- ( Sheila ) What are you doing ? - Going round Dad 's .
What about supper ?
What supper ? You didn 't tell me anything ?
Don 't give me that ! Of course you knew .
What else do I do every evening ?
Just put it in the fridge . I can have it tomorrow .
Vince , you are pushing me to the edge , do you know that ?
Eat your dinner , then you can go to your dad 's .
- Leave it out , Mum . - Well , what are you going to eat ?
Stacy 's making a curry .
Who 's Stacy ?
His new bird .
He didn 't tell you ?
( front door shuts )
( tuts )
( camera clicks )
0h ! Freezing out there !
( Vince ) I thought you 'd be back at six .
Long queue in the post ofﬁce .
You 'd think it 'd be empty after Christmas .
( Vince ) Starving here !
Forgot already what you were hanging on about last night ?
Fridge dinners and all that ?
Or have you gone oft the idea of stale food ...
Oh , sorry .
I didn 't know you had company .
How 's it going , Gwen ?
- ( Vince ) She 's modelling . - Pardon me , then .
I 'm cooking for three then , am I ?
- Gwen ? Vince ? Anyone ? - Yes , please .
Have you offered her anything ?
We only just started .
Gwen , would you like a drink ?
Let 's have a look .
( sighs )
Very good ! He 's made you look really lovely , Gwen .
| wish I had that talent .
( Gwen moans softly )
( Vince moans softly )
( Gwen moans loudly )
( phone rings )
( Sheila on answerphone ) You 've reached 01632 960786 .
I 'm not in right now , but if you leave a message ,
lll get straight back to you .
( answerphone beeps )
( man ) This is a message for Sheila . lt 's Adonis . Box number 1592 .
I got your letter and your photo .
I 've got a few other dates this week ,
but give me a call and I 'll see if i can slot you in .
My number is 01632 960322 .
( strong accent ) A purchase on a horizon ,
a panoply of temptation .
Can a curious soul desist ?
I 'm just looking. thank you .
The hesitation in your voice soon to be an echo
in the recesses of the spheres of retail .
( hushed conversation )
Imagine , 60 percent vanished from this sensational garment .
In apprehensions lie the crevices of clarity .
( Sheila ) Isn 't it a little risque ?
A provocation . For what else must one wear ?
I 'm just going on a date .
A date ? Well ? And what kind of date ? Food and drinks ?
Food and drinks , yeah .
An embellishment of occasion , for instance ,
but also the emphasis of comfort and pleasure .
Thus you will destroy two birds with a stone .
( shop assistant gasps )
Imagine , the dress is your image
and from me onto what you project through an illusion .
One sensation of mind , one fabric in recollection of touch .
( sighs )
But this is how I see your night romance .
I predict the fantasy .
Isn 't it small ? What size is this ?
Thirty-six .
But I 'm not a thirty-six .
In a number is only the equation of actuality .
Dimensions and proportions transcend the prisms of our measurements .
- You 're not getting any more in ? - ( tuts )
( exhales )
There 's a lucky man somewhere in the vista of this mysterious mirror .
May I ask his name ?
His name 's Adonis .
Adonis ? I see him .
I like him .
And it 's not clinging too tightly here ?
Desist warning attention to the askew perception of self .
Lightest trivia and the local vectors of frivolity
are the topics Adonis will be discussing tonight .
I don 't normally wear this kind of thing .
Darings eclipse the dark circumference of caution .
Be bold . Your date will compliment you .
( air escapes )
( capsule rattles through tubes )
Touch it .
Feel it here .
And may I interest you in other desired supposes in our exclusive boutique ?
I 'm ﬁne for now , thank you .
Then I would like you to announce your locus of residence
followed by the numbers to your telephone .
Sheila Woolchapel ,
16 Ferndale Road , Thames Valley-on-Thames .
01632 960786 .
( hushed , echoing voices )
( abrupt silence )
( metallic clunk )
( air escapes )
Thank you .
The pleasure is all mine , Sheila Woolchapel .
Adonis will be waiting and he will compliment you .
- ( chime ) - ( automated voice ) Till number one .
( buzzer sounds )
( coins rattle )
( phone rings )
( assistant ) Sheila Woo / chapel ,
16 Ferndale Road , Thames Valley-on-Thames .
Telephonic code :
zero and one and six and three and two and nine and six and zero
and seven and eight and six and stop .
( Gwen ) Well , maybe I can actually , you know ...
No , I 'm not .
I 'm off . Your dinner 's in the fridge .
( Vince ) What have you done to your hair ?
Why ?
Looks like the council cut it .
Thanks .
You 're not dating , are you ?
Why ? Aren 't I allowed to ?
Bit soon ?
( exhales ) I didn 't know there was a time limit .
I thought you wanted to get back with Dad .
That was a while ago , and obviously your dad had other ideas .
Oh , and tell that femme fatale of yours to get off the phone .
It 's gonna cost me a fortune .
( Sheila on answerphone ) You 've reached 01632 960786 .
l 'm not in right now , but if you leave a message I 'll get straight back to you .
( answerphone beeps )
( Adonis ) lt 's Adonis again .
Amesos Greek restaurant , 7 : 30 .
Ill be wearing a dark Donningtonio suit and oan 'ying a rose .
l 'm tall , slim , short back and sides .
If you don 't ﬁnd me , Ill ﬁnd you .
0h !
- ( Adonis ) Box number 1592 ? - ( Sheila ) Yeah .
- ( Adonis ) Did I scare you ? - No , it 's ﬁne .
( Adonis ) I 've got some love vouchers that will give us ten percent off
as long as we share the same pudding .
Pudding ? Sounds good . Join me .
( opens briefcase )
( rustling )
- As promised . - Oh , thank you .
- What ? - You look different .
How ?
Well , your hair .
Hair grows back .
( creaking )
- Do you know what you 're having ? - ( Adonis ) In a minute , 0K ?
The moussaka looks good .
( Sheila ) So , you like dancing then ?
Not tonight , I sprained my ankle .
God , I didn 't mean tonight . Just in general . You like dancing ?
Yeah .
It says in your lonely hearts advertisement that you like laughing .
What kind of things ?
Funny things .
- What about cooking ? - What is this , an exam ?
( waiter ) Friendly evenings , guests .
Welcome to Amesos . My name is Vlassis and you are ?
Sheila Woolchapel .
Adonis Jackson .
( Vlassis ) And may I take your lucky orders ?
Madam ?
Oh , there will be the lzatziki for the starter
and vegetable moussaka for the main .
Instantly , madam . You , sir ?
Um ... ( clears throat ) I will come back for your lucky order .
{ Adonis munches noisily )
( sighs )
Vince ? Vince ? Get a move on . l 'm desperate . Vince ?
Sorry , I didn 't know you were staying over .
( Gwen ) Didn 't Vince tell you ?
Well , maybe I didn 't hear .
I hope it 's not a problem .
Of course not , no .
Nice night out ?
Yes , thank you . Caught up with a friend .
Where 's Vince ? He didn 't answer when I called him .
He must 've knocked himself out .
It 's always the way with him . As soon as he comes , he 's out for the count .
Must be the pressure of those mock exams .
It should get better by February .
Did you get anything nice in the sales ?
Not much . You ?
I found a very tasteful pair of Carpathian stockings
from Bentley and Soper 's . Seventy percent off .
Now that 's what I call a bargain .
I 'm sorry if I was too long in the shower .
I won 't keep you waiting as I know you 're desperate .
( metallic squeak )
( creaking )
( excited chatter )
( applause )
( sighs )
- ( Vince ) What are you doing ? - You tell me .
- How did this end up in here ? - ( Vince ) Eh ?
The next time your girlfriend wants to try something on ,
how about asking me ﬁrst ?
- ( Vince ) You got a screw loose ? - Don 't talk to me like that .
( Vince ) Gwen wouldn 't be seen dead in something like that .
- So how did it end up in there , then ? - How would I know ?
I don 't like people going through my things , Vince .
- Touche ! Neither do I. - Don 't you touché me .
I 've had enough of her making a mini-bar from my wine
and now helping herself to my wardrobe .
She 's turning my house into a boudoir and I 'm not having it .
It 's becoming a bit disgusting if you must know .
Leave it out , Mum .
No , I 'm not going to leave it out , young Vincent .
I 'll say it again because nothing gets through your head .
To be frank , I find Gwen a bit disgusting .
And the sooner you take that on board , the better .
( echoing voices )
( echoing yell )
( Sheila ) Hello .
( Sheila ) I hope you didn 't move without me .
Don 't get paranoid , Mum .
Now where were we ?
Your turn , Don Juan .
- Oh , my God , what 's that ? - What ?
That looks nasty .
Just some sort of rash .
Ugh , I hope it isn 't catchy .
Yeah , what is that ? I saw it the other day .
I don 't know . An allergy of some sort . Maybe the washing powder .
- You should get it looked at , Mum . - Don 't scare me .
I 'm not scaring you . Just get a cream and Bob 's your uncle . For your sake .
( Gwen ) Myﬁnancial advisor had something similar .
Some kind of blood infection .
Ended up having to amputate her right arm .
- ( Vince scoffs ) Don 't give me that . - Seriously !
The doctor kept sending her home saying it was some kind of allergy
and she ended up really ill .
But it 's ﬁne now .
She eventually learnt to write left-handed .
Beautiful handwriting too .
Your turn .
( dice rattles )
( Vince ) Oh , dear .
Tough decision .
( whirs loudly )
( Vince in French )
( Gwen in French )
Do you have to talk French all the time ?
He has to practise for his A levels .
{ loud clanging )
Actually .
( washing machine whirs in distance )
- Sorry . - ( exhales )
- ( laughs ) - ( distant clatter )
( Vince ) What was that ?
- ( Sheila ) Turn it off . - ( Vince ) I 've turned it off !
Pull the plug out !
( scraping )
Sit on it or something ! 0h !
- ( slicing ) - ( screams )
( heavy thudding )
( Vince ) Mum !
- ( thudding intensiﬁes ) - ( Sheila groans )
( Sheila screams )
What 's going on with this thing ?
( metallic screeching )
( 9 '35 " )
( exhales sharply )
( exhales )
( indistinct )
- ( chime ) - ( automated voice ) Till number two .
( man ) Thanks for coming in , Sheila .
Look at that , still ﬁnding pine needles everywhere . ( laughs )
Allover our sofa back home as well . Must get a plastic tree next year .
Yeah , we must . How 's it going , Sheila ?
- Yeah , everything 's fine . - ( man ) Ah .
What happened to your hand ?
Nothing much . Washing machine went bananas .
Well , we know a very good repair company if you need anyone .
- What 's that , Staverton 's ? - Yeah . Staverton 's Wash . In your area .
They did wonders with our machine , didn 't they , Clive ?
Yeah , they did . A really good mechanic .
So how are things going ? Do you feel on top of things at the moment ?
Yeah , I think so .
We didn 't see you at the Christmas bowling the other week .
Oh , I think I had a lot on with my son that night .
Hmm . Interesting .
Sheila , Pete Mathinson spoke to us the other day .
Now he 's really impressed with how you 're all doing . Lots of good feedback .
Yeah , he also noticed how attuned you were to the Waingel 's Wavelength .
Yeah . One thing he ﬂagged with us though .
He wasn 't sure about your handshake .
Pete thinks you 're doing really well , likes the way you smell as well ,
but to tell you the truth , the handshake did come up
and Pete commented on how perhaps it wasn 't meaningful enough .
Sheila , Pete wanted you to have this article here .
Um ... It 's about the importance of a meaningful handshake .
Sure , I 'll take a look .
( man ) It 's written in a fun , easy language
and there 's a cartoon at the end that summarises the key points .
And Sheila , if you want , we 'd be happy to try out a role-play scenario
- which involves handshaking . - It doesn 't have to be a bank scenario .
We have a range of costumes we could all try on .
- It 's OK , I 'll practise at home . - Hm .
One other thing , Sheila .
One of your colleagues noticed that you tend to visit the ladies ' room
prior to clocking out for feeding time .
Who told you this ?
It wouldn 't be professional of us to say her name .
I normally clock out and instantly leave the building .
Well , if it 's a one-off we understand ,
but we just wanted to ﬂag it up with you , in case Pete ﬁnds out .
A minute or two might not seem significant ,
but when we spoke to your colleague ,
she did some calculations and rightly reminded us
that if these unwarranted toilet visits were to take place
at an estimate of two minutes per visit ,
you would accrue over four hundred minutes every year .
And to tell you the truth , two minutes for a visit to the toilet is generous .
Well , in my experience its two and a half .
I timed myself right before this meeting .
( sighs ) It was a one-off , I can assure you .
Whoever it was who informed you of my transgression
obviously doesn 't notice that I 'm regularly in ten minutes early .
Maybe you could do the maths on that .
- What do you think ? - Is fantastic .
And the shawl ?
The shawlest vantage praises January customer
for she is in purchase of our sacred domain . Cheers .
It 's a little tight around the shoulders .
I knew I 'd need a size up after Christmas .
When your stature is emphasised , it is my duty to provide you
with a notion of proportion that reflects your ideal of dimension .
Wait here .
( eerie echoing noise )
Our perspectives on the spectres of mortality
must not be compromised by an askew index of commerce .
- ( ripping ) - ( assistant gasps )
I 'm sorry .
The model , the afﬂiction .
What happened ?
A calamity .
Imagine . Jill Woodmere . Yes , she .
Our range in garments she defined through a rapture ofdisplay .
And here , the last dress she wore . Oh , how she adored it .
I 'm sorry .
The rhombic coat ?
The rhombic coat , yes . I 'll try it on .
Sorry , one last thing .
How many of those dresses were in stock ?
One . Only the one .
And the model wore that same dress ?
Yes . But imagine , she extensively showered before that photograph .
( moans )
( Sheila ) Vince ?
( knocking at door )
Vince ?
( dialling tone )
( gentle , old Greek music )
Zach ? Sheila , box number 6832 .
I have some love vouchers here with some exciting discounts .
That 's if you don 't mind sharing a pudding with me .
( vibrator buzzes )
- ( moans ) - ( vibrator buzzes )
( moaning continues )
- ( Zach ) You look familiar , you know ? - Oh , no , don 't scare me .
Seriously , I 've seen you somewhere before , I don 't know where , but ...
Do you bank at Waingel 's ?
Ah , I thought it was something like that .
I remember now . You ﬁned me for going over my limit !
Oh , not me , I don 't fine . I just follow orders from above .
I think I still have a letter from you
asking me to make an appointment with your managers .
You were kind of stem , but I liked it .
( laughs )
{ distant moaning )
( vibrator buzzes )
( Gwen screams )
( screams echo )
( screams )
- What happened ? What happened ? - ( screams )
( Vince ) It 's OK , it 's OK .
- ( Gwen pants ) - ( Vince ) Come here , it 's OK .
( slow song )
It 's hard to make friends in this town .
I know .
Is itjust me ?
No , it 's OK . Don 't think about it .
It 's hard to make friends here , it really is .
You met many others through this ?
A few . You ?
One or two . ( sighs )
I don 't need to meet anyone anymore .
Me neither .
" You who wear me will know me . "
What 's that supposed to mean ?
( Zach ) It 's just a design feature .
Cheap bit of mystery .
You think anyone buying these things gives a damn what it all means ?
( scrapes pan )
Would you think I 'm bonkers
lfl told you I think something 's wrong with that dress ?
( Zach ) Of course not .
I haven 't met a woman who didn 't think there was something wrong with a dress .
A woman who modelled it died .
And ? Half the clothes I bought in the charity shop are from people who died .
Don 't run yourself around all this hocus pocus .
Personally , I like you in it .
- Really ? - ( Zach ) Yeah , really .
- You 're not just saying that ? - ( Zach ) You look good in it .
OK , you look good in most things ,
but that dress deﬁnitely shows you off .
Put it on .
Don 't tell me you 're scared of a dress ?
( Zach ) You don 't want to go into town today ?
Oh , it 's a nightmare on Saturdays .
Why don 't we stay here ? You know , acclimatise you to Vince .
No one 's rushing you there .
ljust think it 'll be good for him to see me back on my feet a little bit .
He was a little short with me on the phone .
- He 's in a bad way . - ( man shouts in the distance )
The separation really got to him .
Not helped by my ex trying to pit him against me .
- ( Zach ) Join the club . - ( man ) Darren !
- ( screams ) - ( dog growls )
- No ! - ( man ) Darren , get off !
Get off ! Get off , Darren !
- Darren , get off ! - ( fabric rr 'ps )
- ( Zach ) Get off ! Get off ! - ( screams ) My leg !
- ( dog growls ) - ( Zach ) Get it off !
- ( fabric rr 'ps ) - ( screams )
( man ) Darren , you bastard ! Darren !
- ( door slams ) - ( Vince ) Mum !
- Mum ! - Up here !
( Vince ) Took me ages to get your stuff !
They asked for my ID and everything then they gave me some punk 's rucksack .
I 've no idea why they ...
Vince , this is Zach .
A friend from work .
Pleased to meet you .
All right . Where do you want me to put these , then ?
No point , they 're all ripped to pieces .
Eh ? This one 's not ripped .
- Of course it 's ripped . - It 's brand spanking new , almost .
It should be ripped .
The dog ripped it to pieces . It should be ripped !
I tell you , it should be ripped !
( metallic squeaking )
( pants )
- ( pants ) - ( metallic squeaking )
( metallic squeaking )
l have reached the dimension of remorse , Sheila Woolchapel . The dress .
I can 't claim with its reacceptance if its purchase is not evidenced .
I had the receipt .
I don 't know where it 's gone .
Look , honestly , I don 't need the refund .
Just let me exchange it for something else .
A casual exchange seldom expresses a lady 's self-assurance
- and her embodiment of fashion ... - You know what ? Just take the dress .
I don 't need anything back , just take it .
Lamentations can be fairly addressed to Miss Kolliston .
Distinction avows her noble hearing . Psst ! Psst !
Forget it .
Like a whisper in an ocean , like a feather in a storm ,
a dress of deduction ﬁnds its character in a prism of retail abstraction .
I don 't understand .
Miss Luckmoore experienced a transaction of ecstasy ,
and | ask if you could mutually sanctity her claim ?
Look , this is nothing personal , but I 'm done with the sales , thank you .
But your dismissal of such a prestigious consumerist festivity leaves me bereft .
Did Miss Luckmoore engage with the doctrine of the store
and did the experience consolidate your perception of the paradigm of retail ?
I 've got to go back to work .
Just a goodwill gesture for the inaugural consumer .
A fantastic offer , I inferred to myself in jest .
I just don 't see why I couldn 't return this dress .
The very purpose of this seasonal retail occasion is to expunge .
Returning what has already left
the ladies ' fashion boutique of Bentley and Soper 's Trusted Department Store
goes against the nature of things .
Such a pretty dress .
I hope Adonis complimented you .
Pitcroft !
( door opens )
- ( door closes ) - How 's your leg , Sheila ?
( man ) Better , thank you .
Clive knows the local vet
and he can confirm that he destroyed the dog on your behalf .
( Clive ) He also wanted you to know
that he took great pleasure in denying the dog its last biscuit .
It must be a pain not being able to drive .
The doctor reckons I can start back tomorrow .
Oh , good , good . Um , Sheila , can we have a word ?
Of course .
( sighs )
How was your weekend ?
Well , interesting .
( Clive ) Anything nice in the sales ?
Just a dress , but that was the other week .
Good bargains .
Sheila , I was pleased to see your name down on the bowling list again .
Even though I don 't think you should be in Ruth 's team , but still ,
we have a nice balance of numbers this month , so well done .
Should be an interesting match .
Yeah . Looking fonrvard to it .
Now , Sheila , we caught up with Pete Mathinson this morning .
Really meaningful meeting , um ...
just reviewing where we 're going with various things .
He was very impressed with how you 're getting on , all good .
Only he mentioned that you waved at his mistress
just by Landrake 's tuck shop last weekend .
Yeah , I remember , she waved back .
Hm . You see , she asked Pete to call up a meeting about the incident
and we all came to the conclusion
that the waving can only be construed as informal salutation .
I don 't understand .
Technically , the mistress of a boss is classiﬁed as a superior
according to company policy ,
hence her surprise at such a casual mode ofgreeting .
Yeah , she urged us to term it as insolent Salutation
but she gets ahead of herself sometimes .
She smiled . She waved back !
Sheila , when we worked at the other branch in town
we had a member of staff very similar to you ; diligent , hard working .
Only , Clive and I noticed a core of the inscrutable about her .
Not remotely on the Waingel 's Wavelength .
We didn 't think anything of it until we discovered she was in the habit
of injecting foolhardy substances into her bloodstream on a regular basis .
( Clive ) Now we 're not suggesting you 're inclined that way .
But nonetheless , a story shared and all that .
And those mysterious toilet breaks before feeding time .
One mysterious toilet break .
You would tell us if there was something ?
Then we can keep Pete and the Police Force out of this .
Well , it 'sjust been busy with my son and the school holidays .
What 's wrong , Sheila ? You can tell us .
Nothing ! Just a few bad sleeping dreams .
Can you give us an example ?
Well , just this one the other night , urn ...
I was very close to my mother , in real life , I mean .
My father died when I was young and she and I grew even closer .
I loved her dearly .
I didn 't have enough space to store all her things after she died ,
which always makes me sad .
I gave everything to charity , but wished I 'd kept something .
But in this sleep , i found one of her old dresses .
lt smelt of her perfume , which I hadn 't come across in years .
Brought me right back , made everything feel all right again .
lput the dress on and I looked in the mirror ,
but it wasn 't me at all .
It was my mother from the grave
with the same jet-black dyed hair .
I remember when she bought this dye .
She was so fed up of the old ones dripping off in the rain ,
but this one was permanent . More than her ﬂesh .
I caught a bus and everyone hid under their seats when they saw me .
Racists .
I stank of my mother 's corpse .
The stench made the driver vomit
and we went off a cliff and I woke up .
And what colour was the bus ?
It was the colour of Thames Valley-on-Thames .
Yeah , it was that colour .
( door slams )
I 'm dropping some stuff off at the charity shop
if you 've got anything that needs taking .
Is that a yes or a no ?
( Vince ) Maybe !
Well , you go on Monday , then .
And don 't forget to bring the stuff on the back seat . Yes ?
( Vince ) Yes !
OK . I 'll see you in the morning . I 've left you some food in the fridge .
( Vince ) Where are you going ?
I 'm gonna stay with someone .
( Vince ) What ? You mean slaphead ?
His name 's Zach .
( Vince ) I thought you said he was a mate .
Well , he 's something more than that now .
( woman on radio ) What I always do is , because I love queueing for the sales ,
i ﬁnd it really exciting , and l have done it all night , actually .
Yes , it 's great fun .
There 's a great camaraderie , you know .
And everybody 's good . They keep your place
But the advice i always give , when you go in , don 't follow the crowd ,
because they all go up the main central escalator .
But I always dive to the side of the store
where i know there 's another staircase and run up there to the ﬁrst ﬂoor
because i know what I want because l 'd been the week before
and I knew i wanted this , you know , particular dress .
- And there it was ... - ( Sheila gasps )
( car engine revs )
- ( screams ) - ( tyres soreech )
( screams )
( glass smashes )
( groans )
( 9 '35 " )
( phone rings )
( ringing continues )
( Sheila , upset ) You 've reached 01632 960786 .
l 'm not in right now , but if you leave a message I 'll get straight back to you .
( answerphone beeps )
( woman ) Pick up the phone , it 's the Police Force .
Pick up the phone this instant .
- ( shop bell rings ) - ( man reads football scores on radio )
( clothes rack squeaks )
( assistant ) If you need anything , don 't hesitate to ask .
( woman ) Oh , thank you .
Oh , that does look nice on you .
Really ? I might freeze to death in this .
Think about your summer cruise along the Adriatic
with the breeze running through that dress
as you sip your sparkling wine with the captain on deck .
- ( shop bell rings ) - ( door closes )
( sighs ) I can 't afford a cruise this summer .
Well , if you need any help , just let me know .
( woman ) Thank you .
( man ) All right , mate . Just that , please .
Welcome to Amesos , dear guest . My name is Sandro . And you are ?
Uh ... Reg Speaks .
( Sandro ) May I take your lucky order ?
Just a kebab will be fine . And chips .
Kebab and chips , instantly .
Uh ... Sorry , no bags on the table . Is not nice . And drinks ?
- ( men cheer ) - Reggie !
( men chant ) Down it ! Down it ! Down it ! Down it ! Down it !
- ( cheering ) - ( man ) Oi , oi !
I 'm soaked !
( man laughs ) Never mind , Reg . Never mind .
As your best man , I come equipped , excuse me , for every eventuality .
You need new clothing ? Look no further . ( laughs )
I always knew you had a feminine side .
What choice has he got with Babs around ?
Well , don 'tjust look at it . I didn 't just buy it for the missus , you know !
- I can 't put it on in here . - ( mimics ) " I can 't put it on in here . "
- Go on , get it on . - It won 't fit me .
It 'll ﬁt you , don 't worry about that , go on .
Yeah , come on , you big girl 's blouse , get it on !
- Come on , Reg ! Don 't let the side down ! - ( laughter )
( cheering )
Wait , wait , wait , wait , wait , wait .
- Wait , where 's the dummy ? - Oi ! Clipper !
( laughter )
( man ) Speech ! Speech
( men chant ) Speech ! Speech ! Speech ! Speech ! Speech ! Speech !
Oh , you bloody tosspot . I 'll do it , all right ?
Reg here has been hanging around my house ,
or more specifically , my daughter 's bedroom , since he was 17 .
Now we all love Reg , don 't we ? Don 't we ?
I mean , he always gets a round in , good at five-a-side ,
and I gotta say , he 's always good around Babs .
And that ain 't no easy task .
- You can say that again . - ( laughter )
But seriously , we 've got a good ' un here .
He 's solid , our Reg .
But if you ever , ever mess with my Babs ,
I 'll take you straight down , make no mistake . You got that ?
Steady on , Bananas .
No , no , it has to be said . Best to get it out of the way now .
- Now come on , son . Give us a hug ! - ( men cheer )
- No , no , no , come on , that 's enough ! - Reg Speaks ! I salute you ! ( laughs )
- To Reg and Babs ! - ( men ) To Reg and Babs !
And here 's to your ﬁrst divorce !
Oi , 0 ! Less of that , all right ?
( disco music )
( men jeering in the distance )
( voice echoes )
( echoing voice continues )
( men laugh )
( women ) But he doesn 't have to roll his eyes at every suggestion I make .
It 's always this " I know better " attitude whenever I deal with Andre .
At this rate , I 'll get Reg to DJ , assuming he recovers .
It 's a chamber of booze and methane in here .
I 'm surprised it hasn 't killed the canary .
No idea .
He 'll stuff it down him and it 's always the same . He never puts on any weight .
No idea how the jammy bastard does it . It 's so unfair .
( canary cheeps )
Look , let me know if Andre is willing to be more flexible with the music
otherwise we don 't pay . Simple as that .
Exactly . See you later .
0 ! Stop squeezing my spots , yeah ?
Knew that would wake you .
Just ease it on , Babs .
Good night , then ?
Wish I had a tape of you banging on about how you weren 't gonna drink .
It 's not the drink , it 's just a dirty kebab .
Yeah , right . Don 't know why you hang outwith that lot .
You know what they 'll get you into .
We didn 't do anything . It 's just a dirty kebab .
Dirty kebab my arse , Reg Speaks .
All you had to do was not accept the drinks .
I didn 't want to let the side down .
You gonna lay in bed like that all day ?
You know Andre now wants to do a soundcheck ?
( groans )
What 's a ... What 's a soundcheck ?
He wants to check all the gear .
He says it takes three hours . It 's gonna cut right through the wedding .
It 's just playing records , innit ?
Well , you speak to him , then .
I can 't deal with that weasel-mouthed diva any more .
Every time I question something ,
hejust comes back at me claiming he 's a perfectionist .
Not now , yeah ?
- What 's that ? - Huh ? What ?
( screwdriver clicks )
Oi ! Cottrell wants to take you on .
( sighs ) About what ?
You didn 't invite him to the stag .
But , | - | didn 't think it was his thing .
You try telling that to Cottrell .
Gary said you wanted to see me .
( woman ) So how Iong 's it gonna take to get that spare whatever you call it ?
- Probably about ten days . - ( woman ) Ten days ?
Well , could be sooner if I can get one of my colleagues to drop it over .
- Too busy to do it yourself ? - I 'll be on my honeymoon then .
Honeymoon ? Oh . Congratulations .
And what 's the destination ? Tenerlfe ?
Uh , Lost John 's Cave . Up in Lancs .
- The wife 's got a thing about caves . - ( woman ) Oh .
- Already calling her the wife ? - She 's called me worse .
And what 's the wife 's name ?
Her name 's Babs . She works at Ambrook 's Razors , dispatch manager .
Ambrook 's ? Yeah , my sister used to go out with a bloke from Ambrook 's .
Really nice fella , too .
Oh , that , um ... that must be Phil Keeble .
Why ? No one else nice at Ambrook 's ?
What 's your ﬁancee like ?
She 's all right , yeah .
How long have you been together ?
Fourteen , ﬁfteen years . Something like that .
( woman ) Why get married now ?
I dunno . It 'sjust always been Babs .
You 've never been out with anyone else ?
- ( Reg ) No . - Never tempted ?
Not really . It 'sjust Babs .
( woman ) You 're telling me you never ever get tempted ?
You never even look at another woman walking down the street ?
I can see there 's also a problem with the way the belt rides over the pump pulley .
Small-talk time 's up , then ?
I 've got Mrs Beckley up the road at ﬁve .
Really ?
What 's your name , young sir ?
Uh , Reg Speaks .
Reg Speaks .
My ex-husband used to say he never looked at other women .
He 's probably selling the same lie to his new wife as we speak .
What I 'd give to know what goes on in the male mind .
Any thoughts ?
It doesn 't ride properly over the transmission drive .
All that tension on the belt
is creating havoc with the washers on the clutch shalt .
The transmission mounting bolts have come loose ,
which might have been affecting the washer .
The clutch assembly seems to have lost connection with the low-speed solenoid ,
but I can check the motor wiring at the transmission block .
The agitator hub seems to be intact along with the transmission shaft ,
but the plungers are no Iongerfitting into the wigwags .
If you let me have a look at the wigwag terminals ,
I can be more specific about the problem ,
but looking at it now ,
I can see the wigwag drive shaft is no longer working ... ( voice fades )
( no sound )
Why did you invite Chris Dale to the wedding ?
Not now .
In other words , yet another pointless guest of yours .
- He taught me judo . - Yeah , when you were 17
and even then you legged it when Roj Lines wanted your dinner money !
Half the people on that list never bothered to invite us to their weddings .
And you can deﬁnitely drop Greg and Tina .
- Why ? - Because they invited themselves !
Other thing with them is that opens the door to Dave and Sarah ,
Justin and Linda , Nick and Charlie , and Adrian and Russ .
Invite Greg and Tina
and you automatically have to invite those jokers as well .
Nip it in the bud .
- Are you listening ? - Yes !
( Babs ) Look .
What do you think ?
It 's all right , yeah .
Wash the stink out and it could be all right on me .
You like me in it ?
Yeah . Maybe try it with some tights .
Why ?
I dunno . It 's a bit nippy out there .
I 've told you a million times , they make my legs itch .
You don 't need anything else with this .
It 's ﬁne by itself , look .
Where did Clipper get it from ?
Some shop or other , I dunno .
It 's a size 36 .
How come you fit into it ?
Yeah .
- You listening ? - I like it , yeah !
( Babs ) You don 't get it , do you ? How comes you ﬁt into a size 36 ?
( eerie echoing noise )
( echoing voices )
Reg !
- ( Reg ) Not the ﬂeece ! - It stinks ! Wear the other one .
( Mr Lundy whispers ) Like a whisper in an ocean , like a feather in a storm ,
a dress of deduction ﬁnds its character in a prism of retail abstraction .
( Babs ) See ? It 's a 38 and it 's tight .
- Get a size up , then . - ( Babs ) So , you think it 's tight ?
No , I thought that 's what you just said .
( mutters ) Bloody useless .
( groans )
( sighs )
( man groans )
Villainy ! Now the horrid repercussions will abate your rank , madam !
You !
( Babs ) Over 45 minutes they had me on hold and then the line goes dead .
That 's my whole lunch break gone .
( Reg ) You could 've had your sandwiches while you were on hold .
( Babs ) How am I supposed to eat if I 'm all worked up like that ?
I should 've never gone for that store card .
All that bloody hassle just for a stupid free umbrella
which you ended up losing .
Even when I went in there to try and cancel it ,
the woman kept me waiting for 30 minutes .
No apology , nothing .
Reg ?
Reg ? Reg , are you listening ?
( woman ) Let me just try this on you .
See if it ﬁts .
There , that 'll keep you warm and cosy .
He 's very patient , isn 't he ? Not like most of the boys we get in here .
What 's your name , young sir ?
( Bab ) Reginald ! Get a move on or we 're going to miss the badminton .
You need to ask Clipper where he got it from .
Knowing him , it 's some second-hand shop .
( Reg ) What 's that got to do with it ?
( Babs ) Think about it ! We both got the same rash , we both wore the dress .
You never heard of scabies ?
Reg ? Reg !
W hat ?
- ( Babs ) You think we 'll need a new one ? - Hopefully not . Let 's see , yeah ?
- ( Babs ) What was wrong with it ? - Basket drive went bananas .
The basket drive ?
Yeah , the basket drive . Just went bananas .
And the spin tube bearings are knackered .
I tried to check the clutch surface for any damage
and found that the rivets were rubbing up against the clutch pulley .
There 's also the possibility that the drain hose is kinked ,
but I can put that into writing for you after a more thorough inspection .
The clutch plate is no longer a plate
and the switch striker is neither switching nor striking .
Ifl can get to the wigwag solenoid ,
there is a chance I can ﬁnd out why the washer didn 't drain .
The blocked pump isn 't helping matters and the agitator leaves me at a loss .
I can also see that the wigwag terminals are not where they 're supposed to be ,
which leads me to the conclusion
that this washing machine is dysfunctional ...
( voice fades )
( wind howls )
( screwdriver clicks )
- Oi ! Cottrell 's looking for you . - What now ?
One of your neighbours reported you . Just tell me you didn 't do it .
I had to , it was an emergency .
You know the rules , Reg !
You fix your own machine , it still has to go through the books .
- I bought my own spare parts . - And ? Who paid for your training ?
You 've really let the side down , do you know that ?
Now get in there before Cottrell takes me on as well .
( sniffs )
- ( Babs ) I 've had it with Andre . - ( door slams )
If he vetoes one more song .
I 'm gonna stick that turntable up his miserable backside !
( Bananas ) Where 'd you learn to talk like that ?
Oh , it 's easy for you to say . You 're not the one having to deal with him .
Every time I say no to something , he just says , " Why ? Why ? Why ? "
( Reg ) Maybe I can make a compilation tape .
- Save us a bit of money too . - You 're joking , right ?
Your record collection wouldn 't even get a flea jumping .
Ease it on , Babs . I 'm only trying to help .
( Babs ) What 's this doing down here ?
( Reg ) Sorry , I didn 't see that there .
- What are you doing ? They stay there . - Why ?
( groans loudly )
Now come in the kitchen you two . I 've got a cheesecake for you both .
Oh , lovely . Cheers , darling .
You 're not worried ?
- About what ? - That .
It 's probably just the washing powder we use .
- You don 't think it 's scabies ? - No .
- An allergy ? - No .
- Something venereal ? - You tell me .
- I haven 't slept around . - Me neither .
- Does that mean you love me , then ? - Yeah .
( canary cheeps )
( wings ﬂap frantically )
( clattering )
( Babs ) She 's asphyxiated .
( Reg ) How can a dress asphyxiate it ?
Well , how else did she die ? She 's barely a year old .
- Could be carbon monoxide . - We 'd be dead then .
- Not if it 's a small leak . - You 're scaring me now .
I 'll come back and take a look on my lunch break .
No way can you get home and back in an hour .
- If the ﬂame turns orange , call me . - Yeah , yeah .
What are you doing ?
Uh ... You 're going to be late .
Go ! Before Cottrell shoves a ﬁrework up your backside .
Reg , go ! I 've got to do my hair .
( Clive ) Thanks for coming in , Reg .
When our neighbour heard you were coming in for a loan ,
- he wanted to pass on his greetings . - Oh , who was that ?
( Clive ) Mr Watlington , your physics teacher .
Oh , right .
( man ) He also wanted to pass on his apologies for hitting you so often .
It 's OK .
It was a bit of a Reg Speaks evening , in fact .
( chuckles ) He kept telling us about you at school ,
and to tell you the truth , he was sad to hear about your ﬁnances
when we showed him your loan application .
Now , with that in mind , of course ,
we 'd love to consider your thoughtful request .
But given that Staverton 's kicked you out ,
we 're somewhat reluctant to sign it off .
What about here ? I heard there was a job going .
( Clive ) Sorry , that 's taken , I 'm afraid .
Though I did see a sign at Dentley and Sopers saying they were looking for someone
in the male alliance of clothing and costume .
No , no , but looking in the sense
- that one of the staff has disappeared . - Oh .
They 'rejust trying to ﬁnd him . They 're not advertising a job .
Oh , silly me . It 's my mistake .
Now , the only loan we can offer is the deferred employment package .
DEP .
It 's what we like to call a motivational loan .
It helps our customers get back on their feet
and back into the job market .
With that kind of interest rate ?
That 's just advisory .
Reg , Clive and I had someone over from Staverton 's a few years back
and we still think a lot about
how nicely he talked us through the whole process of fixing our machine .
And we thought seeing as we 'll be having Reg Speaks in the room ,
maybe he could do something similar for us ?
It would mean a lot to us , Reg .
But there 's no machine here .
You could pretend there 's one .
( Clive ) Nobody needs to know .
But I can 'tjust ...
Just try . Then we can look at more favourable rates for you .
It 'll be fun .
Um ...
Plungers on old machines tend to stop retracting ,
which means a knock-on effect with the washer .
A-Also the belt drive had come off .
The inlet valve might have been blocked , but I can 't verify that .
It s-seems ...
It 's OK . It 's OK , Reg . No one 's forcing you .
If it helps. we could kick it off in a role-play scenario .
Yeah . A lot of loan applicants ﬁnd our Tudor courtroom scenario
puts them at ease .
( Clive ) Clothes still needed washing then .
That 's right . ( chuckles )
What 's the matter , Reg ?
You spoke so clearly and nicely when you first came in .
Oh , no , um , nothing .
I-I 'm just a bit tender these days , that 's all .
How come ?
Just a sleeping dream I had last night . It 's been on my mind all day .
( Clive ) Interesting .
We 're here for you Reg . Sometimes it can help to discuss these things .
Well , Babs , my fiancee , was in labour .
l was late , so at that point , the door was locked .
I tried to take on her pain just to make her feel better .
( screams )
( no sound )
( Babs screams )
( Reg ) I kept screaming to show how much I cared ,
but it just seemed to annoy everyone .
I kept knocking on the window in the hope that they 'd let me in .
( screams )
( no sound )
The baby came out of Babs in this dress that looked exactly the same
as the one I wore on my stag night at ZinZan 's .
I wanted to wave at my little girl , but she wasn 't having it .
She made it clear that i should sling my hook .
( no sound )
- ( man ) What was her name ? - Babs Junior .
Interesting .
Reminds me ofa dream Stash and I had when we put the sand dunes in the wash .
Oh , yeah , that . Kept bypassing the spin cycle , I remember now .
Was it an old machine ?
No , no , it was brand new . Wasn 't it , Stash ?
Yeah , very strange .
Did you check the belt if it was broken or loose ?
That could have been the problem with it .
( Stash ) That 's what we were wondering , but maybe it was something else .
What do you think , Reg ?
It 's probably a problem with the wigwag and its rotational pull .
Plungers on doors sometimes don 't align with the seal ,
but the lid switch is often to blame .
The inner tub might 've sustained serious dents
resulting in the belt drive loosening or coming oft ,
but that 's usually a problem with older machines .
The lid switch and its actuator , the motor coupler or door lock assembly
are the first things to check when a new machine bypasses the spin cycle .
The agitator drive shaft and spin tube linked to the transmission
can come loose from the tub struts .
If the helix doesn 't release the brake
and the belt tensioner doesn 't allow slippage ... ( voice fades )
Imagine ,
trading will cease at a premature hour on this , the twelfth day of sales .
There lie other boutiques to your discernment .
But I 'm in the store now .
You can 't just turf me out . Customer rules and all that .
You must conclude your perusal immediately , then .
Excuse me ? I 've worked in retail .
Once the customer steps through the door ,
you see it through to the last . That 's what I had to do .
The doors you passed through are doors in perpetual revolve
and thus not a veritable indication
of the time in which you thought you might have set heel
in Dentley and Soper 's Trusted Department Store , mate .
You call those doors revolving ?
Hm-hmm .
Listen , I 'm here to choose a dress , yeah ?
Pick something up , try it on , pay for it , and then leave you in peace .
By the time you 've thought of another excuse to get me out , I 'll be done ,
mate !
This dress . So shabby , so unkempt .
We have rules here about presentation , about hygiene , about conduct .
A required pedigree of shopping
is an aspiration we flowerfully seal to our hearts .
Please , return in a different dress and we will welcome you back .
If you let me buy a new dress , I will .
( in distance ) Psst !
I now announce you extension time . Congratulations .
I never thought I 'd say this ,
but you lot could all do with a good shag .
( both laugh )
( laughs )
( distorted synth music )
Such an intimate document of finesse and joy .
Nice to see a catalogue with ladies bigger than me for once .
Pray tell , your measurements would be ?
- Guess . - Thirty-six .
- Really ? - Thirty-six .
You 're not just saying that ?
Thirty-six .
Thirty-six . I had a sleeping dream I was a size thirty-six .
And I went out with my friends to ZinZan 's to celebrate ,
but it wasn 't ZinZan 's .
It was here .
That was where it was .
It was in this room and in this catalogue .
Every image was of me in this slip getting skinnier and skinnier ,
but the measurements written next to me
were getting bigger and bigger .
I rang the staff bell for assistance .
Two ladies came to my aid and told me
to put my head between my knees
whilst they tried to correct the catalogue .
( whispers ) 36 , 38 .
( whispering )
36 , 38 .
( pencil scribbles )
( whispering continues )
36 , 38 .
( hinges creak )
( thud )
( Babs ) And then they buried me .
Here in this Trusted Department Store .
And then they buried me .
( yawns )
Your changing room is waiting for you
and your dress to coalesce into a simple union ofwonder .
( whispering )
( synth music )
( tannoy ) Attention , consumers . Attention , consumers .
Your shopping will conclude now .
Pay us for your items and return to your houses .
( whispering )
( thud )
( coins jingle )
Thank you very much . Goodbye .
Goodbye to you too , dear Audrey . ( blows kiss ) Fantastic .
There will be this asphodel blouse and a pair of those funeral stockings .
Instantly !
Excuse me , l was here ﬁrst .
No , you weren 't .
Going through that tray doesn 't give you the right to bypass the queue .
You came here after me .
No , I didn 't . Now if you don 't mind ...
Such fascination of marvel .
Its touch to the skin , its contour on the body .
I will be sewed first . There 'll be this cinnamon bra .
Thank you very much .
( gasps ) Ladies !
( gasps ) Hey !
- ( groans ) - ( shoppers gasp )
( distant yelling )
( screaming )
( synth music )
( shoppers yell )
( distant yelling )
( 9 '35 " )
( yelling continues )
( woman screams )
( 9 '35 " )
( alarm sounds )
( Babs pants )
Blame ! Blame !
( alarm continues )
- ( banging on door ) - ( Babs yells )
( Luckmoore ) Blame ! Blame !
( alarm continues )
( tannoy ) A dramatic affliction
has compromised our Trusted Department Store .
Get out graciously .
( screaming )
A dramatic affliction has compromised our Trusted Department Store .
- Get out graciously . - ( Babs cries )
- ( alarm continues ) - ( screaming )
A dramatic affliction has compromised
- our Trusted Department Store . - ( banging )
Get out graciously .
( screaming )
A dramatic affliction has compromised our Trusted Department Store .
Get out graciously .
( evil laughter )
( distorted ) A dramatic affliction has compromised
our Trusted Department Store .
Get out graciously .
( evil laughter )
( distorted ) A dramatic affliction has compromised
our Trusted Department Store . Get out graciously .
( evil laughter )
( distorted ) A dramatic affliction has compromised
our Trusted Department Store . Get out graciously .
( evil laughter )
( alarm continues )
( distorted announcement )
( evil laughter )
( sewing machine whirs )
( lift creaks )
( creaking )
( sewing machine whirs )
( glass crunches underfoot )
( indistinct muttering )
( muttering continues )
( muttering fades )
Subtitles : BTI Studios